This is number 25.
Something's interfering with the transmission.
That's going on.
What's going on?
How is this happening?
What's happening?
Haunt springs.
Warm water that wells from the center of the earth.
They have enchanted humans for ages.
People flock from all over to soak their aching bodies in nature's scalding hot baths.
Healing, relaxing, and revitalizing.
No one can resist their charms.
This is the wave
Thank you.
And I mean, we want the spirits to make discoveries and think for themselves, so I'll make the arrangements.
Besides, we want them happy, right?
No one likes an angry spirit.
Right.
So, where are you going?
I was thinking Tekko Paradise since it's coming.
Yes, that's a great one.
Hey, listen, you should join them.
Give yourself a break.
I can take care of everything for you here.
You must think I'm crazy.
I absolutely do not.
I think you're working too hard and we can't function if our commander is exhausted.
So do us all a favor.
Go to the hot springs.
What are you really after?
I have no idea what you mean.
I have no desire to install several surveillance cameras there.
Would someone like me actually fill a hot spring with lenses so that I could stare at every inch of that hard, tight, young body at my discretion?
Especially the back side.
No, no, not the internment camp.
Please have mercy.
Please forgive me, commander.
Anywhere but there, please.
Listen up, Kanazuki.
When you get to the camp, you're going to start digging a hole and not stop for the entire day.
And after that, you'll fill the hole back up and repeat for a whole week.
Woo-hoo!
The hot springs with my big brother.
We've had word from headquarters.
It's come to my attention that supplementary personnel are currently being deployed from DEM.
And unlike you and your platoon, they've managed to figure out a way to use magic correctly.
Not that I think for a moment you would lose to civilian transfers.
Far from it.
But there's nothing wrong with observing their technique, right?
Roger that, sir.
Um, excuse me, captain.
What is it?
I wanted to ask about the company trip this weekend.
Oh, you mean the 13 Secret Hot Springs Tour?
With all-you-can-eat delicacies from different regions?
Yeah, about that.
So you know how more spirits have been turning up lately?
Well, our alert levels have increased a tiny bit.
What are you saying?
Well, I'm sorry, but the trip has been canceled.
Screw you!
Spirits!
Now, hold on.
Please, let me finish.
Huh?
I know it won't replace the trip, but the troops and I were thinking, why don't we send you to Tengu Paradise Hot Springs?
You deserve some kind of break.
I think a day of relaxation is exactly what you need right now.
It's our way of saying thanks for everything.
Plus, it's already handled, so you have to go.
Thank you.
Very nice work.
I think you just earned a double rank position.
Okay, but I'm not dead.
I can't wait to go.
I love the hot springs.
Best day ever.
Listen up!
The captain has accepted our invitation.
Hot springs are fast!
I do not approve.
This is time that you could be using to train and add power to the team.
One day?
Hello, Shido.
Hey, what's up?
Can I return the book I borrowed from you sometime tomorrow?
Of course, that's fine.
Bye-bye.
Uh, something happened.
Come on, Shido, let's go!
A hot springs paradise!
Okay, you have to stop pulling my shirt!
Sorry, Origami.
I'll talk to you later.
Whoa, she's mad!
Oh, my God, man.
Oh, wow, this is so neat!
Hey, that's right.
I forgot this is the first car ride for you two.
It's pretty cool, isn't it?
Just be careful not to get carsick.
Oh, pet me, too.
Oh.
I don't think I can reach that far.
It's not fair for you to touch her like that and not me.
Come on.
You're the one who said you wanted to sit in the front seat.
Oh, yeah.
Look, Shido, I'm in front of you.
Pet me, too.
Okay.
Who's a cute rat?
Oh, Shido, what's that spinner thing?
Oh, that?
That's a barber pole.
Hey, what about that?
I think it's one of those laundry flanks.
Mom, I'm a dad!
Okay, if you say so.
I never dreamed we would be using the deployment train to take a day trip.
Let's not lose track here.
Our goal is to confirm the operation of the vehicle.
We're making a periodic check of a route we don't normally use.
It's not for fun.
So stop messing around and come to order, troops.
She's having fun.
She's messing around.
Agreed.
The captain's right.
If we're going to the hot springs, we need to be well prepared.
We must document this rare outing.
Hot springs?
Hot springs.
The hell was that?
I'll check!
What is going on out here?
Oh.
Really?
Okay.
The tunnel caved in, so there's an emergency shutdown.
They don't know yet when the service will be restored.
Nothing we can do about it now.
Troops?
Ma'am!
They leave us no choice but to march to our location.
Forward!
Roger!
Will you please forgive me?
That was so cool, Toka!
You broke the entire car just by using...
Cheer up.
It's going to be okay.
Does that mean you're not mad anymore?
No, I'm not mad at all.
Several unknowns are turning up on the radar.
Confirmation needed.
They have been matched.
It's the AST.
The AST?
What are they doing here?
That's strange.
Maybe it's because of the spirits?
I highly doubt it.
They aren't even able to detect spirit waves from Toka and the others right now.
Don't worry about why.
Any contact we make now could interfere with the plan.
Sound the emergency code.
We should wait.
The commander's out on business.
And our second-in-command is busy with this punishment.
Enough!
According to Article 22, Clause 3,
if there's an emergency, we have the right to transfer command.
If at least five crew members agree, we can sound the code.
Dove, hands on sounding the code!
Confirm!
I, Bat-Marriage, Kuwagaway, temporarily accept the role of deputy commander.
Yes!
Deputy commander?
I like the sound of that.
Activate the code!
Form the absolute defense line!
And prepare to attack!
Block the advance of the AST!
Roger!
Yep, I was right.
This is much different from the map.
That street doesn't look familiar.
Captain!
There's a dead end up ahead!
The right flank is also a dead end!
There's a shopping arcade 500 miles straight ahead of us!
Behind us!
The street has been destroyed!
We can't help that.
Hey, Origami.
Ma'am.
Keep watch from up above.
Roger that.
Checking.
There is no shopping arcade over to the left,
but I do see a side road a short distance ahead.
Looks like it connects to the main road after about a quarter of a mile.
That'll work!
Troops, forward, march!
Oh, my gosh.
Kotori, what are you doing here?
Hi!
It's so good to see you!
Hello?
Is there something wrong?
No, not at all.
I was just...
I wanted to make sure that Shida was doing his job.
What?
You can do all that from the ship.
Be real.
You just wanted to come with us to the hot springs, right?
Don't be ridiculous.
Look, it's okay.
Why don't we all go together?
It'll be a lot of fun.
Well, I guess if you insist.
Let's go.
What in the world is going on?
So, if you need anything, just let me know, okay?
Thanks, I guess, but what about you?
I said I'm fine!
I'll catch up with you later.
Okay.
Oh, man.
Why did something have to happen now?
This is starting to get ridiculous.
There was definitely a path plot here.
No reaction here.
Vibration and infrared sensor failed.
No reaction from the acoustic sensor either.
And no humans detected within 500 meters.
The walls around here are a minimum of 50 centimeters thick
and are heavily enforced with rebar.
Like that'll stop me!
Bring it here.
Right.
Troops, attention, please.
About fate!
Forward march!
What just happened here?
Uh-oh.
What's that?
Did I do something just now?
No.
You did nothing.
The wall exploded all by itself.
Oh, no!
That's so scary!
Crap.
It figures.
Looks like the damn AST decided to meddle again.
Switch to Datetown Type 2 in combat mode.
And use whatever firearms you feel are necessary.
Commander?
What are you doing out there?
The site inspection.
Don't worry about me.
Confirm your orders.
Right.
Transitioning to Datetown Type 2 in combat mode.
Eliminating the AST.
What is this?
Rose!
What is happening?
It's so cold.
Move carefully.
This doesn't feel right.
Look alive, ladies.
And hurry!
The commander is watching.
Do whatever it takes to stop them.
Roger.
What's this?
A mobility inhibition system.
It spills a special liquid on the ground to lower friction coefficient to below 0.01.
Meant to prevent the progression of the target.
Damn.
What about the one over there?
Probably some kind of hypnotic gas.
Helpful for when the enemy wants to stop us without killing us.
Well played, whoever you are.
Listen up!
Use the suppression equipment!
Attack immediately!
Helpful for when the enemy wants to stop us.
Where's Yoshinan?
Hey, it's going to be all right.
You're not helping.
The only method that's going to calm her down right now is finding Yoshinan.
Huh?
Ah!
Look.
You and Yoshinan are going to be together again very soon.
Ah!
Shino, please be careful!
Target is City Barrier.
We're breaking through with Labyrinth.
The target is rapidly approaching.
Look out!
Type 2 combat mode won't work to stop them.
So, what's our next tactic?
Do we know if our enemies put up a territory yet?
That has been confirmed, yes.
Alright, well then this next move won't kill them.
You have permission to use destroy mode!
Roger that!
Permission to fire free on Date Town.
All weapons authorized.
Do whatever you must to stop the AST!
I'm exhausted, pissed, and covered in sweat.
I was supposed to be bathing in the hot springs by now.
How the hell did this happen?
Huh, that's right.
The lieutenant commander stresses me out.
The troops said we should go to the hot springs while we're still young.
It's all work and no play!
I'm gonna go there today even if it kills me!
They think they can do whatever they want and we won't retaliate?!
Those boots can't and pieces of junk are pathetic!
The AST will not be defeated!
You should do yourselves a favor and repent!
Alright ladies, give em hell!
Just because it's a work day doesn't mean we can't have a little fun!
So go ahead!
Annihilate, slaughter, eradicate, eliminate, kill, and destroy those pieces of trash!
If any of you have bullets left when this is over, that ammunition will be shoved down your throat!
Use it all!
Fun, isn't it?
I can't hear you!
Aren't we all having fun?!
What is happening?
There aren't any spirits anywhere!
I don't get it!
Always trying to pick fights with me!
Is this what you wanted, you swine?!
You think it's easy to do all this against the spirit?!
No, why don't you try it?!
If you're lucky, you might even be left with a bone or two in your pathetic body!
You're not gonna stay young forever!
I'm busting my ass over here to keep my skin young despite the stress and lack of sleep you cause!
Never underestimate a woman at her peak!
I'm only 27, dammit!
What is up with that voice?
Freaking creepy!
Look out, you guys!
I can't move!
Disarm the territory, or you'll freeze to death!
I got it, thanks!
Are you okay?
She's alright, just some scratches.
Huh?
What?
Yo, Shido!
Here you are!
Stop!
Do you hear me?!
Stop the attack!
Shido!
No!
Radio interference!
Analyzing ground zero!
Here's the video!
You're safe now.
How are you feeling?
I'm good.
Thank you.
What is that?!
Do you think it could be Princess?
Hey, Captain!
Princess showed up!
Now!
I'm good!
Thank you!
What is that?!
Do you think it could be Princess?
Hey, Captain!
Princess showed up!
Now!
I'm good!
Thank you!
What is that?!
Do you think it could be Princess?
Hey, Captain!
Princess showed up!
Now what?
She probably can't hear us!
Huh?
I've got this!
But...
But your attack power...
I don't care!
I'll make it work!
We're gonna live!
So, uh...
Where did Princess come from, anyway?
Do you think it means that everything that happened today was because of the spirits?
I had no idea they could do all this.
We can never let our guard down.
Ah!
Yes!
I feel so much better!
Freaky!
She's so weird!
Guess we finally made it, huh?
We did!
Today sure was hard!
Ah!
It's been quite a journey, hasn't it?
We can finally let loose!
Alright, left face!
And forward, jump!
Oh!
Sure!
Yeah!
Oh!
Did Shido eat?
Going to be tough to relax like that…
Commander, is now a good time?
Kanazuki!
Where did you come?
Here!
I was minding my own business and digging the hole as ordered when suddenly—
I dug up a hot spring!
How is it?
What is it? Does it feel good?
Do you feel less tired now?
It's supposed to relax sore muscles, too.
We're sorry about today.
Yeah, it was all my fault you had to deal with that crazy stuff.
Hey, did you guys do this on purpose?
Maybe. I will say that I'm glad you're recharging.
I've got a lot of work for you to do later.
Gotcha. What a great night.
Talks can help from this table?
Lia and taems can help team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team, team team team team team team team Team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team team.
I'm so happy to be here
It's a long way
I'll keep going with the power of your life
Will you meet again?
Will you trust me?
Will you be looking for love?
I'm so happy to be here
Take the world
The world will end before you
I'm so happy to be here
And I'm so happy
That's my birthday
In particular
Love is so happy today
I'm so happy to be here
How do you guys love?
朝 Svartu
Are you good?
I'm so happy to be here
Time Lobo
You're trying to get started
You